(Bernadette:)I don't think you are.
(Raj:)You didn't think I was gonna be
in your kitchen this morning,
(Raj:)yet here I am.
(Voice:)Psst, hey, kid.
(Sheldon:)Huh, what?
(The Flash(the voice):)You look tired.
(The Flash(the voice):)Why don't you have
an energy drink?
(The Flash(the voice):)Everyone's doing it.
(Sheldon:)Oh, no, thank you,
those have caffeine in them.
(The Flash:)Oh, sorry,
(The Flash:)I thought you were cool.
(Sheldon:)I am cool.
(Sheldon:)This is Yoo-hoo,
(Sheldon:)chocolate milk's
delicious watery cousin.
(The Flash:)All right.
(The Flash:)But if you ever want to feel
like you have superpowers,
(The Flash:)try one of these.
(Sheldon:)Superheroes take
performance-enhancing chemicals?
(The Flash:)You bet.
(The Flash:)You know why Hulk
is so strong?
(The Flash:)Steroids.